# Sam Peterson

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

**(** 

peterson2020@fakeemail.com

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

### **EDUCATION**

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies June 2017 - July 2020

**University of Kwazulu-Natal** 

Bachelor of Computer Science Honours

July 2020 - Present

### **SKILL**

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

### **ABOUT ME**

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **BACK-END DEVELOPER**

Google Inc

**January 2017 - August 2017** 

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was in sync with everything
- Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

#### **PROGRAMMER**

Microsoft

June 2018 - June 2019

- Maintain server
- Provide and facilitate end user assistance
- Maintain computer paraphernalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

#### PERSONAL ASSISTANT

Coca Cola Inc

June 2019 - Present

- Schedule meeting for CEO
- Run errands for the executive
- Take calls and appointments for CEO

## **REFERENCE**

Kutlo Sek, Google Inc

Senior Developer

Email: kutlosek@fakeemail.com

Julian Assad, Wiki Leaks

Ethical Hacker

Email: julian@fakemail.com